

Bē /delgadociterio



### **ABOUT ME**

I am a creative and hard working Informatics Engineer, passionate about web development, specially in the Front-end area. I've been working in the area for more than five years and by now I'm looking for new experiences and interesting challenges.

## **SKILLS**

HTML and HTML5: 9/10 CSS and CSS3: 9/10 JavaScript: 7/10 jQuery: 7/10 Bootstrap: 8/10 Sass: 7/10 Photoshop: 8/10 Wireframing: 9/10 Wordpress: 6/10 GIT: 6.5/10 Linux: 5/10 AngularJs: 6/10 Game Maker: 6.5/10 English: 6/10 Guitar: 4/10

To know more in depth about my skills, go to: http://delgadociterio.com

## **ATTRIBUTES**

- Creative
- Fast Learner

Drawing: 5/10

- Responsible
- Dedicated
- Attentive to Details
- Careful with Projects
- Teamwork

# INTERESTS

- Reading
- Studying English
- Movies
- Gamina

## **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

Universidad Alejandro de Humboldt -Informatics Engineering (2009 - 2014)

- Web Development
- Programing
- Logic
- HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Java
- C++

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Eficiatech - Web-apps Developer (Dec 2014 - Jul 2015 - 8 months)

- Web-apps development
- ROR Development
- HTML, CSS and JS
- Data Bases
- Sass

El Universal - UI/UX Specialist (Jan 2016 - Mar 2017 - 1 year 3 months)

- JavaScript Debugging
- Widgets Development
- Web-pages Development
- Angular Development

WBI Innovations - Front-end Developer (May 2017 - Jun 2018 - 1 year 2 months)

- Wireframing
- Websites Maintenance
- Angular Development
- Wordpress Development
- Development of the itso.int website

Jumperr - Web Developer/Designer (Jun 2018 - Oct 2018 - 5 months)

- Wireframing
- Web Design
- Web Development
- Web Development Support

Advoqt - Frontend Developer (Aug 2019 - Dec 2019 - 5 months)

- Wireframing
- Dashboard Design
- Web Development
- Angular Development

Freelance Front-end Developer (Jan 2019 - Present)

- Wireframing
- Web Design
- Web Development
- Web Maintenance

# **COURSES AND EXPERIENCES**

Curso de Productividad Personal en la Era Digital - Fundación Santa María la Real del Patrimonio Histórico (2017)

Curso de Introducción al Desarrollo Web (Primera Parte) - Universidad de Alicante (2017)

Duolingo English (Competent) (2016)

Adobe Dreamweaver CS6 - Arts (2014)

Adobe Photoshop CC - Arts (2015)

Graphic Design - Visual and Graphic Design - ALISON (2017)